qweas.com 2007-06-16

# Qweas.com Privacy Policy

---  

##  Privacy Policy Statement 

Qweas is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the Qweas.com site (the "Site"); it does not apply to other online or offline Qweas sites, products or services. By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement. 

1\. COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

The official website of Qweas, Qweas.com will collect your personal information when you visit some web pages and subscribe certain services, for example, Newsletters. The personal information including your name and email address will be used to send subscribed services to you. And your personal information will not be shared with any third party companys, personal, or organizations, unless it is declared when you subscribe the service. 

The Site Qweas.com may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and administer the site. Some of our sites collect information about your hardware and software in order to provide a requested service. 

2\. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. 

Subscribe newsletters will collect your information including name and email address that will be used to send newsletters to you. Feedback may collect your information including name and email address that will be used to contact you to talk about the details you report. 

If you are a developer or webmaster who will submit software or website to Qweas.com, our database may also collect your information including company name, email address, information, and so on. 

3\. USE OF COOKIES 

We use cookies on this site to save your favorite visiting habits, for example, advanced search engine parameters. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Web sites you visit. 

You also have the ability to clear your internet tracks and cookies from your web browsers periodly. 

4\. SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

Qweas is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. 

5\. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT 

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top and bottom of the privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 

6\. LINKS 

This site includes many external links point to other websites, for example, software developer's official website. This privacy statement is not repsonsible for external links. Other websites with links from this Web site, including software developers' websites, have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on their links. 

7\. CONTACT INFORMATION 

Qweas welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that Qweas should add more detailed statement to this page, please contact us at: 

**E-mail Address:** [privacy@qweas.net](mailto:privacy@qweas.net?subject=Privacy%20Policy)

**Physical Address:**  
Qweas Ltd.  
No 27, Shangdi East Road, Haidian  
Beijing, China  
Postal Code: 100085
